虚幻勇士冒险 S2E6 XANA崛起 由özberk özen制作
视频来源：https://youtu.be/9KzGvCbcj84 中文字幕由熙洛Chincode制作 翻译：Albeta 校对：jky
What do you think, father? Is this gonna work?
你怎么看 父亲？这能行吗？
I don't know, Aelita. Sorry.
我不知道 Aelita 对不起
Before this happened, we should activate a signal on Lyoko.
在这件事发生之前 我们要在Lyoko上激活一个信号
All right. So, this should be connected to that tower.
好的 那么 这应该是和那个圆塔有关
And if we deactivate it, the flood will stop too.
如果我们锁定它 洪水也会停止
Yes, Odd, you're right. We only need to deactivate the tower.
是的, Odd, 你说得对 我们只需要锁定那座圆塔就行
Yes, I'm a genius!
是的,我是个天才!
But if we go back...
但是如果我们回去...
Your shield will disappear.
你的防护罩就会消失
There must be a way to that.
一定有办法的
Let's see. Well, well, well. Actually, I'm working on a program for that.
让我们看看 办法还是有的 我正在研究一个程序
New program? You're a genius Franz, like me!
新程序？你和我一样是个天才 Franz
Ok, here we go...
好了 我们开始吧...
We will need Yumi too.
我们也需要Yumi一起去
Okay, Jeremy, I'm ready to go.
好的 Jeremy 我已经准备好了
Jeremy? Who are you talking to, Ms. Ishiyama?
Jeremy？你在和谁说话 石山女士？
And program is ready.
程序也准备就绪了
Perfect, then, transfer: Odd, Aelita, Yumi, Ulrich...
很好 那么 传送 Odd, Aelita, Yumi, Ulrich...
Goodbye, Mr. Delmas. Please take care of the students.
再见 Delmas先生 请照顾好学生
Wait, what?! What was that?!
等等 什么？那是什么？
Ms. Ishiyama?
石山女士？
Finally, on our way to Lyoko, I've missed Lyoko!
终于 在我们在去Lyoko的路上了 我已经很想念Lyoko了!
I'm teleporting you all in Desert Sector.
我把你们都传送到了沙漠区
The activated tower is there.
激活的圆塔就在那里
We're in the desert, Einstein.
我们在沙漠里 爱因斯坦
What should we do?
我们应该怎么做?
Find the tower and deactivate it as soon as possible.
找到那座圆塔并尽快锁定它
Send us the vehicles, Einstein.
实体化交通工具给我们 爱因斯坦
Here it is.
这就来了
Ok, the plan is simple. Find the monsters and deactivate the tower.
好的,计划很简单 找到那些怪物然后将圆塔锁定
I wonder what XANA will send us now.
我想知道XANA现在会给我们安排什么
I think XANA will send us mantas or hornets?
我想XANA会送我们飞鹞或飞蚊？
Maybe it's Bloks or Tarantulas?
也许是方文或者是狼蛛？
I win, mantas are here.
我猜中了 飞鹞来了
Ah!
啊!
Aelita! Are you okay?
Aelita 你还好吗？
Yes, I'm fine. Thank you
是的 我很好 谢谢你
Yes, that's it!
是的 就这样吧
Odd, Yumi, the other two is up to you.
Odd, Yumi 其他两个就看你们的了
Don't worry, buddy.
别担心 伙计
Okay, Yumi, let's handle these.
好吧 Yumi 我们来处理这些
Perfect, it's my turn.
太好了 轮到我了
But, wait, I know this feeling.
但是 等等 我知道这种感觉
What do you mean, princess?
你是什么意思 公主？
Jeremy, something's happening.
Jeremy 有情况
I think we've got a problem here.
我想我们这里出问题了
What's that fireball?
那个火球是什么？
XANA created a new monster!
XANA创造了一个新的怪物
It has a lot of life points like a Kolossus.
它的生命值很高 就像熔岩巨人一样
XANA has a new monster, Einstein.
XANA有一个新的怪物 爱因斯坦
And he looks so powerful.
而且他看起来很强
Nooo!
不!
He's too strong!
他太强了
Yumi, noo! You will pay for this, rocks!
Yumi 不！ 你会为此付出代价的 石头
Yumi! Ulrich! Wait
Yumi! Ulrich!  等等
You'll pay for this!
你会为此付出代价的
Oh nooo!
哦 不
Ulrich!
Be more careful, guys. We have to protect Aelita.
多加小心 伙计们 我们必须全力保护Aelita
But it's too strong!
但它太强大了
Aelita, fly away! Find the tower. Go Aelita. Go.
Aelita 快飞走 找到那座塔 去吧 Aelita 快去
Okay, Jeremy!
好的 Jeremy
Aelita, nooo!
Aelita 不
It's okay, Jeremy, I'm inside the tower!
没事的 杰里米 我在圆塔里面
This thing is so powerful.
这个家伙威力太大了
We can launch the return to the past right now.
我们现在就可以启动时间倒转程序了
Return to the past now.
马上时间倒转
I'll call this new monster as Koliseo.
我想给这个新的怪物起名叫Koliseo
Koliseo? It sounds familiar.
Koliseo? 听起来很熟悉
Impossible, all the names I found are unique!
不可能 我找到的所有名字都是独一无二的!
Its name doesn't matter. Still, it's one of the most powerful monsters we've ever faced.
它的名字并不重要 不过 它是我们所遇到的最强大的怪物之一
We've never seen anything like this before.
我们以前从未见过这样的东西
I'm sure we'll see this monster more in our next adventure.
我相信我们在下一次冒险中会看到更多这种怪物
Yes, you will, but you need to be more careful.
是的 你肯定会的 但你需要更加小心
True. If Aelita doesn't have these wings, she will never survived.
确实如此 如果Aelita没有这对翅膀 她就永远无法安全活下来
This monster was very fast. It devirted me so quick.
这个怪物动作非常快 它一下子就打得我逆虚拟了
And it sent me a huge fireball. It is not fair!
而且它给我送来了一个巨大的火球 不公平啊!
XANA never play fair, Odd!
XANA从来都是不公平的 Odd!
Because of this, we will be more quick about the program, Jeremy.
正因为如此 我们要更快地完成计划 Jeremy
You're right, Franz
你说得对 Franz
We need more programs.
我们需要更多的程序
And we will do that!
我们也会做到的!
We will beat XANA as soon as possible.
我们会尽快击败XANA
I'm sure we will do that.
我相信我们会做到这一点
I'd really want to know what it will do next.
我真想知道它接下来会做什么
Actually, I wonder that too.
事实上 我也想知道